Lesson 13. It's only me. After her husband had gone to work. Mrs. Richard sent her children
第13课。只是我。丈夫去上班后。理查德夫人送她的孩子
to school and went upstairs to her bedroom. She was too excited to do any housework that morning.
上学，上楼去她的卧室。那天早上，她太兴奋了，无法做任何家务劳动。
For in the evening she would be going to a fancy dress part with her husband.
在晚上，她将与丈夫一起去一件高档的衣服。
costume: n.   化装服
She intended to dress up as a ghost and as she had made her costume the night before.
她打算打扮成鬼魂，就像前一天晚上做服装一样。
costume: n.   化装服, consist: v.   由……组成, sheet: n.   被单
She was impatient to try it on. Though the costume consisted only of a sheet,
她不耐烦地尝试。尽管服装仅由一张床单组成，但
effective: adj. 有明显效果的，有作用的
it was very effective. After putting it on, Mrs. Richard's went downstairs. She wanted to find out
这非常有效。戴上它后，理查德夫人下楼。她想找出答案
whether it would be comfortable to wear. Just as Mrs. Richard's was entering the dining room,
是否舒适穿。就像理查德夫人进入餐厅一样，
there was a knock on the front door. She knew that it must be the baker. She had told him to come
前门有一个敲门声。她知道那一定是面包师。她告诉他来
straight in if ever she failed to open the door and to leave the bread on. The kitchen table,
直到她都没有打开门，把面包放在上面。厨房桌子，
not wanting to frighten the poor man. Mrs. Richard's quickly hid in the small storeroom under the stairs.
不想吓train穷人。理查德夫人迅速藏在楼梯下面的小仓库中。
She heard the front door open and heavy footsteps in the hall. Suddenly the door of the storeroom
她听到前门打开，大厅里的脚步很重。突然的仓库门
was opened and a man entered. Mrs. Richard's realized that it must be the man from the electricity
被打开，一个男人进入。理查德夫人意识到这一定是电力的人
board who had come to read the. Meater. She tried to explain the situation, saying, it's only me.
来阅读的董事会。meater。她试图解释情况，说，这只是我。
pace: n.   一步
But it was too late. The man let out cry and jump back several paces. When Mrs. Richard's walked
但是为时已晚。该男子哭了起来，跳了起来。当理查德夫人走路时
slam: v.   砰地关上
towards him. He fled, slamming the door behind him.
对他。他逃跑了，猛击了身后的门。